Most often we hear the expression ‘Vaiṣṇava sevā’.
Molto spesso sentiamo l'espressione "Vaiṣṇava sevā".
[Vaishnava Seva | Guru is Not Alone]
[Vaiṣṇava sevā | Il Guru Non È Da Solo]
Gurudev, guru we take to be the best,
Gurudeva, il guru che consideriamo essere il migliore.
vaiṣṇava śreṣṭha—the best amongst the Vaiṣṇavas.
Vaiṣṇava śreṣṭha: il migliore tra i Vaiṣṇava.
So it’s also, in one sense, under the heading of Vaiṣṇava sevā.
Allora è anche, in un certo senso, sotto il titolo di Vaiṣṇava sevā.
Serve guru and Vaiṣṇav.
Servi il guru e i Vaiṣṇav.
I worship the guru along with his associates.
Io adoro il guru insieme ai suoi associati.
He has friends, servitors, servitor-friends …
Lui ha amici, servitori, amici-servitori...
So, it is a … It would be a mistake on our part
Dunque, è un... sarebbe un errore da parte nostra
to try and see guru in isolation.
provare a vedere il guru in isolamento.
praṇamāmi ca caraṇāntika- paricāraka-sahitam— [Pr-jivan]
praṇamāmi ca caraṇāntika- paricāraka-sahitam— [Pj]
“I worship guru along with his paraphernalia.”
"Io adoro il guru con tutto il suo armamentario",
(His or her paraphernalia).
armamentario di lui o di lei.
Means, those who are dear to guru,
Ossia, quelli che sono cari al guru,
those who are infused with similar dedication as guru.
coloro che sono infusi da una dedizione simile a quella del guru.
As we do not see Kṛṣṇa in isolation,
Così come non vediamo Kṛṣṇa isolato,
we do not see Śrīmatī Rādhārāṇī
non vediamo Śrīmatī Rādhārāṇī isolata,
we do not see guru in isolation.
non vediamo il guru isolato.
We are worshippers of the Vaiṣṇava.
Siamo adoratori dei Vaiṣṇava.